const questionsData = [
  {
    question: "How many layers are there in the OSI Model?",
    options: ["5", "7", "6", "8"],
    answer: "7",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for establishing, managing, and terminating connections between applications?",
    options: [
      "Transport Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Session Layer",
      "Application Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Session Layer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for data encryption?",
    options: [
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Transport Layer",
      "Presentation Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Presentation Layer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the OSI model, which layer is responsible for routing packets across different networks?",
    options: [
      "Physical Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Application Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Network Layer",
  },
  {
    question: "At which OSI layer does IP operate?",
    options: [
      "Physical Layer",
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Transport Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Network Layer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following OSI layers handles flow control and error control at the segment level?",
    options: [
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Transport Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Application Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Transport Layer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which protocol operates at the Transport Layer of the OSI model?",
    options: ["HTTP", "TCP", "IP", "ARP"],
    answer: "TCP",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the unit of data called at the Data Link Layer?",
    options: ["Packet", "Frame", "Segment", "Bit"],
    answer: "Frame",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which OSI layer converts the electrical signals into data frames?",
    options: [
      "Physical Layer",
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Transport Layer",
      "Network Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Data Link Layer",
  },
  {
    question: "At which layer does the MAC address operate in the OSI model?",
    options: [
      "Physical Layer",
      "Data Link Layer",
      "Network Layer",
      "Transport Layer",
    ],
    answer: "Data Link Layer",
  },
];

export default questionsData

